autoalert.com 2016-06-16

# FuzeCast Privacy Policy - Auto Dealer Data Mining Lead Generation

### **Please read this privacy policy carefully. It applies to all interactions you have with FuzeCast’s product and services.**

##### THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you create an account with FuzeCast, you give us your full name and email address, and create a username and password. If you want, you can give us a pseudonym instead of your legal name.

If you don’t feel like creating an account from scratch, you may be able to sign in through an account you already have with another service, such as Facebook.

Your user profile helps you customize your account and connect with other FuzeCast users. Your profile automatically includes your name and username. You can also add a profile picture.

To help you connect with other FuzeCast users and to personalize your FuzeCast experience, we may ask for additional information, including your contacts, location or a list of the apps on your mobile device.

We receive some other information automatically when you use FuzeCast. This includes data about your device, software, operating system, operating system-provided device or user-specific advertising IDs for advertisement tracking (“AdvertisingIDs”), you IP address and the date and time of each request you make to FuzeCast.

So that we can make your FuzeCast experience better, we collect information about how you view, flip and interact with context and advertisements through FuzeCast and on third-party sites with FuzeCast widgets.

You may link your FuzeCast account to other services you use, such as social networking sites, photo-sharing services and media publisher such as the New York Times. If you connect your FuzeCast account with a third-party service, we collect information through that service. This information varies depending on the service and your privacy settings there, but may include profile information (e.g., age, gender, and location), your contacts on that service and content that you’ve made publicly available there.

If you want to email something you see through FuzeCast to a friend who isn’t already a FuzeCast account holder, we may keep their email address for the purpose of sending such email and improving our services. Recipients may contact us at [privacy@FuzeCast.com](mailto:privacy@FuzeCast.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

### HOW WE USE AND DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION

A big part of FuzeCast is sharing content you find interesting. That’s why your FuzeCast profile, the people and sources you follow, the magazines you create, the comments you post and the content your flip are all public.

Aside from that, we use your information to keep FuzeCast running, better understand how you use our service, customize your experience (including the content, marketing materials, and advertisements you see), prevent abuse and improve FuzeCast.

**We share your personally identifiable information only under these circumstances:**

With your consent, after letting you know what information will be shared, and with who.

If we believe it’s reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal process. If we’re going to release your information, our policy is to provide you with reasonable advance notice under the circumstances unless we’re prohibited from doing so by law or court order (e.g., an order under 18 U.S.C. 2705(b)). We may disclose your information without giving you prior notice if we believe it’s necessary to prevent imminent and serious bodily harm to a person. Nothing in this privacy policy is intended to limit any legal objections or defenses you might have to efforts by third parties to compel disclosure of your information, including legal orders from the government.

To third parties helping us offer and improve our services, such as those providing FuzeCast certain technical tools and analytics services (including marking partners) that help us understand how people use FuzeCast so we can make it better. We require those companies to observe the limitations in this privacy policy.

If we sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of your assets, including the information identified in this privacy policy, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets in the event of a bankruptcy. We may also share non-personally identifiable, non-aggregate information (for example, anonymized Advertising IDs) with companies that help us improve our products and services, including advertising(such as research companies and analytics providers). As with your personally identifiable information, we require that such companies observe the limitation in this privacy policy.

We may disclose aggregate information about how our users use FuzeCast in a manner doesn’t identify you individually.

### WEB STORAGE AND TRACKING POLICY

Cookies and HTML5 local storage are ways to keep information about your use of Internet services on your own mobile device or computer.

We use cookies and HTML5 local storage to help us create your session, know when you’re logged in and help us remember certain information about how you interact with FuzeCast.

If you’d rather not use cookies or HTML5 local storage, most browsers give you the option to turn them off, or require your approval before using them to keep information. If you choose not to keep information in cookies or HTML5 local storage, though, portions of FuzeCast may not work as intended.

FuzeCast also uses web beacons in advertisements to allow FuzeCast and its advertising partners to see how users view and engage with advertisements. Depending on your advertising preferences set in your operating system, FuzeCast may share your Advertising ID with advertising partners in an anonymous fashion that is not tied to your name or email address.

Some publishers or other third-party services that we partner with may use cookies, web beacons or other technologies to keep track of your Internet activity. Please note that this privacy policy explains FuzeCast’s policy only, and doesn’t cover the practices of other services.

Some browsers make it possible for you to signal that you don’t want your Internet browsing activity to be tracked. The Internet community hasn’t reached a consensus on how to best honor these signals, so we don’t respond to Do-Not-Track requests at this time.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

As FuzeCast continues to develop, we may decide to revise this privacy policy from time to time. The most current version will govern our use of your information and will always be at https://fuzecast.com/privacy, and older versions are available upon request. If we make changes that we think will substantially alter your rights, we will notify you by posting a notice on our website. You agree to accept any changes or revisions to this privacy policy by continuing to use FuzeCast.

### CONTACT

We’d love to hear you questions, concerns and feedback about this privacy policy. If you have suggestions for us, let us know at support@autoalert.com.
